

Personal Profile

As a dedicated learner

passion for coding and

captivating websites. My journey started with a

development, and through

continuous learning and

budding professional in this field. I specialize

friendly and visually

a positive impact on

appealing websites, and my main goal is to make

users' web experiences.

and opportunities as I

continue to grow and

excel in this ever-

evolving industry.

embracing new challenges

practical experience, I've grown into a

who has now become a

Developer, I have developed a genuine

the art of crafting

strong desire to

in creating user-

I'm excited about

understand web

Juni or Frontend

Bogdan Zafiescu

Junior front-End Developer

Web Skills

- Web development using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Experience with responsive design
- Fundamental knowledge of j Query
- Familiarity with Google
 Maps API, including markers
 and information windows
- Basic understanding of Bootstrap 5
- Familiarity with HTTP requests and AJAX data transfer
- Basic knowledge of Photoshop and GIMP

Linux skills

- Completed fundamental course in Linux(ubuntu)
- Experience with Linux command line
- Basic Linux system administration, networking and security.
- Fundamental knowledge of FTP and HTTP/HTTPS server and client
- Experience with other Linux distros (Debian, Manjiro and Fedora)

Additional technical skills

- Completed fundamental course in Java
- Basic knowledge of C
- Competent in using Windows operating system
- Familiarity with virtualization technologies (VMWare, Virtual Box)
- Familiarity with remote desktop technologies
- Hardware knowledge

1

Education and Training

Techni cal:

- Codecademy certificate of completion: Learn CSS Course (2022)
- Codecademy certificate of completion: Learn HTML Course (2022)
- Bit Academy certificate of completion: Frontend Web Development HTML & CSS (2022)
- Bit Academy certificate of completion: Frontend Web Development JavaScript (2022)
- Bit Academy certificate of completion: Java Programming Fundamentals (2019)
- Cisco Networking Academy certificate of completion: NDG Linux Unhatched (2021)
- Linked In Learning certificate of completion: Learning Java (2019)

Other:

- 2009 2010 Romanian Aviation Academy, Flight Attendant Certificate & license
- 1999 2003 Henri Coanda Technical College of Aeronautics, Highschool Diploma, Baccalaureate Diploma
- 2003 Machine Repair and Maintenance Certificate

Work Experience

Quality Control for Apple @ Syncreon, Tilburg, Netherlands 2020 - 2021

- Conducted thorough quality control checks on Apple products to ensure they met the company's standards.
- Inspected products for scratches, dents, and other damage, and ensured that they were clean and functional.

Quality Control @ Intrarom, Romania, Bucharest 2019-2020

- Conducting various tests on Fixed Wireless Access devices
- Monitoring results and recording any failures or errors

Lift Operator && Ticket Checker @Killington Pico Ski Resort, Vermont, USA 2018 - 2019

• Ensured the safety and enjoyment of guests by maintaining lift operations and verifying tickets.

Cosmetics Sales Specialist

- @ Soap and Co, London, United Kingdom, 2017 2018 &&
- Sakare Cosmetics, Berlin, Germany 2016 2017
 - Provided exceptional customer service, personalized product recommendations, and exceeded sales targets using ethical practices.

More Experience

Assistant Waiter @ Carnival Cruise Lines, Miami, Florida, USA 2013 - 2016

• Assisted in restaurant food service aboard Carnival cruise ships, ensuring excellent customer experience.

Juni or Dental Techni ci an @ Dent Total, Romani a, Bucuresti

2008 - 2009

• Assisted in the fabrication of dental prosthetics and maintained laboratory equipment.

Juni or Vi deo Editor @ Multi Media Est SRL, Bucharest, Romania 2006 - 2008

- Received tapes and copied them using various media equipment.
- Made necessary modifications as requested by directors and transferred final products to digital disks or uploaded to FTP servers.

IT Technician @ Victor PC Repair, Bucharest, Romania 2004 - 2006

- Performed maintenance on PCs and replaced parts such as motherboards, processors, etc.
- Cleaned and optimized computer performance.
- Installed software and operating systems for clients.
- Assisted clients in building their home networks and connecting to neighboring networks.
- Changed cartridges and installed printers.
- Configured clients' firewalls and provided technical advice on security best practices.

Languages

English: B2

French: A2

Italian: A1

Hobbi es

IT,
DIY,
Hi ki ng,
Group
Acti vi ti es,
Coffee